PRASHANT BHANGE

Project Management

Started professional career in November 2014 and now looking for a job profile which will give an opportunity to grow and gain experience while achieving the set goals of the organization. Following is work experience in past 7 years.



Work Experience

2019-10 -Current

Block Operating Leader

Atyati Technologies Pvt. Ltd, Ahmedabad

- Assist to State Head.
- Liaisoning with bank officials for existing and new mandate's
- Identification processing and deployment of BCs at allotted locations through team of district coordinators.
- Monitoring & Back-end support to 100+ BCs.
- Daily follow-up with BCs & District Manager
- Educate BCs about their roles and responsibilities.
- Motivating the team/BCs to achieve organizational & Bank goals.
- Provide Kiosk Software Regarding Technical Support or training.
- Responsible for Maintaining MIS Reports.

2017-08 -2019-06

Head of Project Management (DDU-GKY)

Global reach Skill Training India Pvt. Ltd, Aurangabad

End-to-end ownership of implementation of DDU-KGY and other government funded/learner paid skill development projects in the state, executed by endeavor Career. This role will include establishing and monitoring the following components of the overall project operation

 Building the team for successful implementation from scratch - recruitment and training of trainers/mobilizers and other vertical employees within aligned timelines with support from HQ





Contact

Address

Ahmedabad, India 382424

Phone

+918390000459

E-mail

pbhange05@gmail.com



Skills

Team leader

Very Good

[Technical Support to BC] Proficiency

Excellent

Advance excel skill

Excellent

Microsoft Power BI

 Building robust mobilization mechanisms across the state to ensure timely student enrolment in line with project mandate

- Placement Support Working with regional/HQ placement team to ensure quality placement of trained candidates as per project mandate
- Overall Project Management Ensuring delivery of aligned topline/profitability goals and timely collections as an outcome of successful project management.

2014-11 - Office Administrator

RattanIndia Nasik Power Ltd, Nasik

- General Office Administration
- General Human Resources Management
- Team Member Joining and On-boarding
- Article Trainees' Interview and Shortlisting
- Attendance and Leave Management
- Timesheet Management
- Office Laptop Inventory Management
- Attendance and Leave Management
- Statutory compliances
- Employee Engagement Events
- Monthly Conveyance Reports

Education

2011-06 -2013-05

2017-08

Bachelor of Arts (BA): Public Administration and Services

Lokmanya Tilak Mahavidyalay - Maharashtra



Desktop

Language-Marathi, Hindi, English.

Good

Tally ERP 9

Excellent

Microsoft Power Point

Excellent